[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
There are no corndogs in hell.
Alright, well, daylight's burning,
[machine gun fire]
I guess there's no...
Oh! OH!
Oof!
Will you give me FIVE
SECONDS to turn this around?!
No, you won't!
Fuck you!
Fuck you...
What the hell?! This one's shut, too?!
There's not like a little crack...?
No! There's nothing!
Fine! Abandon ship!
I've had mixed feelings about
this boat every step of the way.
Is he firing aga--AHH!
Perfect.
Okay, where is he? I didn't even see him.
I STILL don't see him.
[machine gun fire]
Whoa!
How does he...?
Yeah, no, I'm not doing this.
Son of a bitch can't control his
recoil, but he sure can aim straight.
Of course. Locked.
That's a BIG-ass lock.
Hey, I couldn't shoot it, could...? No...
No...
I mean, yes!
Wow. The power of no-yes.
I'd shoot more doors open if I didn't
think that would just jam up the locks.
Plus, that would imply
I know where I'm going.
Oh wow! A Magnum just
lying here in the basement.
This must be where the staff
plays Russian Roulette.
Maybe during their lunch break.
WHOA!
AH!
Now, where did y--
Jeez, this thing stings!
I wouldn't have used THIS gun
if I had known you were coming,
but convenience won out.
But I also didn't KNOW you
were coming--you didn't knock.
I mean, what'd you expect me to do,
just shoot through the door
as soon as I heard a noise?
It looked pretty solid.
Oh! Maybe THAT'S why the Magnum was there.
Although, you know what would better
is if everybody wasn't
trying to FUCKING KILL ME?!
Ah! Shit, what am I doing?
Here, let me just calm down...
...kill everyone...
...then I'll have some time to think.
But this keeps HAPPENING!
I need to start thinking
more outside the box on this.
I mean, I still need to
kill everybody, but--AHH!
What the hell?
[Hunter-Chopper firing]
OH! Oh! Oh! Oh!
WHERE'D THE CHOPPER COME FROM?!
I DIDN'T HEAR ANYTHING!
FOR FUCK'S SAKE!
[Hunter-Chopper firing]
Oh! Oh!
If only I had a high caliber weapon that
could really punch through its armor!
C'mon... Eat it...
[Hunter-Chopper firing]
Yeee!
THIS IS BULLSHIT! THOSE WERE GOOD SHOTS!
I KNOW THOSE WERE GOOD SHOTS!
DAMMIT, WHY DID CIA TAKE AWAY
MY WEAPONS?! I HAD AN RPG!
"THOSE ARE GOVERNMENT
PROPERTY. I NEED TO TAKE THOSE.
"NOW HERE'S A REALLY DANGEROUS MISSION."
MOVE!
Fuck... Did that come out of him?!
Oh, I don't even want to THINK about that!
[Hunter-Chopper charging up]
It's spinning up! Where is it?!
I don't see it!
[Hunter-Chopper firing]
Ooh-hoo!
BLAH!
JESUS CHRIST!
WHERE IS IT?!
[Hunter-Chopper charging up]
Fucking gravel...!
AND HE'S SAFE!
YEAH! TRY TO FLY IN HERE, ASSHOLE!
[loud machine gun fire]
AAAAH! AAAH!
[ears ringing]
I DID IT AGAIN!
IT FEELS AWFUL!
I'm going to be like Grandpa Mitch!
Well, assuming I live that long!
I sure PLAN on living that long!
But fate and I seem to be having
a really abusive relationship.
Oh! Indoors! We're safe here!
DID YOU HEAR?! WE'RE SAFE HERE!
WE'RE SAFE! HOORAY!
OH NO! WE'RE NOT SAFE!
EVERYTHING'S STILL TERRIBLE!
LIKE ALL THE OTHER TIMES!
GET AWAY FROM ME!
RAAAAH! NO TIME!
AS SOON AS I'M DONE RELOADING, SOMEBODY
ELSE IS LIKE, "AAH, COME KILL ME!"
SEE?!
INTELLIGENCE ONLY MEANS SO MUCH
IF YOU HAVE NO TIME TO PREPARE
AND HAVE TO DO EVERYTHING ON THE SPOT!
JUST SCREAM AND HOP AROUND
UNTIL YOU'RE SHOT!
WHAT A GREAT EQUALIZER!
IT'S NOT GOING TO STOP, EITHER!
Even RIGHT NOW, I'm giving that chopper
three minutes before it says, "Eh, fuck it,"
and starts blind firing into the warehouse.
Christ!
I'M OUT!
Just kidding.
I mean, I AM out, but not TOTALLY out.
Y'know, a technicality.
See, if I had time to prepare, I could
rig up a mannequin, spray paint it orange,
attach a motor on wheels to it...
I'm sure the chopper would light it up for
20 minutes before it realized it's not me.
But that's not the point here, is it?
I've got it now. I'm here
to dance for the CIA.
See, I thought they were incompetent
because I thought they actually
wanted to DO something.
THAT was my mistake.
They have teleporters.
If they wanted this over, they could just
teleport the leader into space. Pop. Done.
But that's an existential threat,
because if they can solve all
conflict, that makes them superfluous.
And who knows how long
this has been going on;
I'm sure they've had
these thoughts years ago
so I don't know where their minds' at now,
but it seems to be at the bored god phase.
[Hunter-Chopper firing]
So, n--AAH AAAAH!
Yeah, that's what I get for
thinking above my paygrade!
WELL, IT *USED* TO BE MY PAYGRADE!
Although my pay was still kind of shit.
It's just how the man keeps
you down. With attack-choppers.
This isn't doing anything!
We're not communicating at all!
YOU'RE NOT LISTENING!
HERE! CATCH!
Oh, great! GREAT!
Nnnnngh!
[explosion]
Yeah, yeah. Get it out of your system.
Okay, I can move this, but...
I'm getting soft in my old age. The younger
me wouldn't waste a grenade to save time.
BLAH! WHY YOU GOTTA BE LIKE THAT?!
YOU'RE JUST MAKING ME REGRET THIS EVEN
MORE KNOWING YOU WOULD'VE MOVED IT!
WELL, NOW YOU CAN'T! YOU MISSED YOUR CHANCE!
[gibbering]
NO ONE UNDERSTANDS ME!
So, yeah. That's the
mission. Not to fight aliens,
but for the CIA's bosses to
feel something--anything.
By not giving me what I need, that makes
their hearts beat just a little bit faster.
They're so numb to watching agents
die, they need more. And that's me.
Fuck...
[Hunter-Chopper charging up]
[Hunter-Chopper firing]
Christ, for all I know, they're
the ones piloting the helicopter!
Ngh!
[machine gun fire]
AAAAH! AAAAH!
It's like those people who hunt wolves
from a helicopter! Really sporting!
GIVES YOU THE REAL THRILL OF THE HUNT!
C-fucking-I-A...
Nope!
You're being evicted. I don't
even want to hear your excuses.
AAAH! NO! STOP! DDYAAAAAH!
This is my ONLY cover. I HAVE to take it!
I hope you guys didn't leave a mess for me!
Okay, you did--OH-HO-HOO!
[Hunter-Chopper firing]
Oh! Cover!
Wait, what's this?
Does it work?
JESUS! IT'S STILL NOT GOING THROUGH!
Well, I saw SOMETHING.
There was an explosion!
PLEASE REMAIN STILL!
I'M A SCIENTIST! I NEED
TO REPRODUCE MY RESULTS!
FINDINGS ARE ENCOURAGING!
BUT IT'S NOT ENOUGH SAMPLES!
WE NEED TO BE THOROUGH!
NO! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?! STOP IT!
YOU'RE INTRODUCING A NEW VARIABLE!
IF YOU KEEP THIS UP, YOU'RE
GOING TO SKEW THE RESULTS!
NO!
OH, NOW YOU'VE DONE IT!
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO START ALL OVER!
NO! COME BACK! THE
EXPERIMENT'S NOT FINISHED YET!
Typical test subject...
This is why science
takes so long. Right here.
Is he coming back?
Maybe?
No...
So if that WAS CIA, that explains a lot.
It's almost as if I have to
save them from themselves.
They've grown bored of
killing their own agents,
but then they do it from the
safest vantage point possible,
so they deny themselves the rush.
What's this?
[alarms sound]
Oh! And there it is!
I just needed to press a button!
Was that so hard?
Well...yes. Yes, it kind of was.
The CIA should've just put ME in
charge of teleportation technology.
I would never go insane with power.